[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The plastic cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Is the medium RedUnknown cube lighter than the small plastic cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has lower friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium bamboo cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the small wood cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small wood cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small plastic cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the small wood cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2163?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium bamboo cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the small wood cube collide with the medium RedUnknown cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small wood cube and the small plastic cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the small wood cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The small plastic cube and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the medium redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The small plastic cube and the medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The small wood cube and the medium bamboo cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube and the small wood cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium bamboo cube and the wall"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Will the small wood cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1}]